A Guide to the Plats and certificates of the Virginia Land Office, 1779-1982
Library of Virginia
- 1785
  - McG, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - McK-McM, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - McN-McR, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Me, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Mic-Miller, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Mills-Mitchell, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Mof-Mon, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Moo-Mos, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Moylan, John, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Mu-My, 1785. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Na-Nel, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Nev-New, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - No-Nu, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Od-Os, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Ow, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Pad-Pat, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Pau-Pay, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Pe, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Pi-Pl, 1785. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Po, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Pri, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Pru-Py, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Q, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Ra, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Re, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Read, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Ri, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Roa-Rob, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Rod-Ros, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Ru, 1785. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Sa, 1785. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Sc, 1785. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Se, 1785. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Sh, 1785. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Si-Sm, 1785. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Smith (Amos-Joseph), 1785. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Smith (Henry-Samuel), 1785. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Smith (Thomas-William), 1785. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Sn-So, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Sp, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Sta, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Ste-Sto, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Str-Su, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Sw-Sy, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Ta, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Te, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Th, 1785. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Ti, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Tilton, William, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Tilton, William, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Tilton, William, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - To, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Tr, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Tudor, George, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Tu-Ty, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - U, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - V, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Wad-Wal, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - War-Wat, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - We, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Wh, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Wild-Wilk, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Will, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Wils-Wit, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Wo-Wr, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Y, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Z, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 10)
- 1786
  - Ad-Al, 1786. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Am-An, 1786. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ar-At, 1786. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Ba, 1786. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Banks, Henry (Botetourt Co., No. 1-19), 1786. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Banks, Henry (Botetourt Co., No. 20-39), 1786. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Banks, Henry (Botetourt Co., No. 40-59), 1786. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Banks, Henry (Bototourt Co.), 1786. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Banks, Henry (Greenbrier Co.), 1786. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Banks, Henry (Greenbrier Co.), 1786. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Banks, Henry (Harrison Co.), 1786. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Banks, Henry (Harrison Co.), 1786. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Banks, Henry (Harrison Co.), 1786. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Banks, Henry (Monongalia Co.), 1786. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Banks, Henry (Montgomery Co.), 1786. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Banks, Henry (Montgomery Co.), 1786. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Banks, Henry (Rockbridge Co.), 1786. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Banks, Henry (Rockbridge Co.), 1786. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Banks, Henry (Warrants), 1786. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Be, 1786. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Bi-Bl, 1786. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Bo, 1786. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Bond, Dr. Thomas, 1786. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Br, 1786. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Bu-By, 1786. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Cal-Cam, 1786. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Can-Car, 1786. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Ce, 1786. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Ch, 1786. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Cl, 1786. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Claiborne, Richard, 1786. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Co, 1786. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Cr, 1786. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Cu-Cy, 1786. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - C - Miscellaneous, 1786. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Da, 1786. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - De-Di, 1786. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Do-Du, 1786. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - E, 1786. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Fa-Fe, 1786. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Fi-Fu, 1786. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Ga, 1786. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Gallatin, Albert, 1786. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Gh-Gi, 1786. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Gl-Go, 1786. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Gr-Gw, 1786. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Gratz, Bernard and Michael, 1786. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Hac-Hap, 1786. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Harb-Harr, 1786. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Hart-Haz, 1786. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - He, 1786. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Hi, 1786. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Hob-Hou, 1786. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Howard, 1786. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Hu, 1786. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - H - unidentified, 1786. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - I, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Ja, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Jo, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - K, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - La, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Lawrence, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Le, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Li, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Lo, 1786. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Lu-Ly, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - L - unidentified, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - McCall-McClury, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - McColley-McWilliams, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Mac-Man, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Mar-Mat, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Mason, Richard, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Me, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Mi, 1786. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Mo, 1786. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Mu, 1786. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - M - unidentified, 1786. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Na-Ne, 1786. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Ni-Nu, 1786. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - O, 1786. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Pa-Pe, 1786. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Ph-Pi, 1786. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Pl-Pr, 1786. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Pu, 1786. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Q, 1786. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Ra-Re, 1786. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Reed, John, 1786. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Rh-Ri, 1786. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Roa-Rob, 1786. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Rog-Rou, 1786. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Ru-Ry, 1786. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Sa, 1786. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Say, Dr. Benjamin, 1786. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Sc-Se, 1786. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Sh-Sl, 1786. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Sm-Sp, 1786. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Sta-Stuart, John, 1786. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Stuart, William-Sw, 1786. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Ta-Te, 1786. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Taylor, Thomas Augustus, 1786. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Th-Ti, 1786. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Tr-Tu, 1786. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - V, 1786. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Vanderen, John Jr., 1786. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Wa, 1786. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - We, 1786. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - West, Stephen, 1786. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Wh, 1786. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Wic-Wilmoth, 1786. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Wilson-Wit, 1786. (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, James, 1786. (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Wo-Wr, 1786. (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Wynkoop, Benjamin, 1786. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Y, 1786. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Z, 1786. (Box 70, Folder 3)
- 1787
  - Ab-Ad, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Al, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - An-Ap, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Ar, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - As-Ay, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Bac-Ban, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Banks, Henry, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Barg-Barn, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Barr-Bax, 1787. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Be, 1787. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Bi-Bl, 1787. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Bo, 1787. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Bra-Bri, 1787. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Bro-Bry, 1787. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Bu-By, 1787. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Cab-Cal, 1787. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Cam, 1787. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Can-Caw, 1787. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Ce-Ci, 1787. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Cl, 1787. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Cob-Con, 1787. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Coo-Coz, 1787. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Cr, 1787. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Cu, 1787. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Dam-Daw, 1787. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Davidson/Davison, 1787. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Dea-Dem, 1787. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Den-Di, 1787. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Do, 1787. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Dr-Dy, 1787. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Ea-El, 1787. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - En-Ew, 1787. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Fa-Fi, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Fl-Fo, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Forde, Standish, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Fr-Fu, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Ga-Ge, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Gi, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Go, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Gr, 1787. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Michael Gratz and Co., 1787. (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Gu-Gw, 1787. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Hai-Ham, 1787. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Han, 1787. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Harb-Harr, 1787. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Hars-Hay, 1787. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Hea-Henderson, 1787. (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Henderson, Alexander, 1787. (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Hendricks-Het, 1787. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Hi, 1787. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Hod-Hoo, 1787. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Hop-How, 1787. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Hud-Hum, 1787. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Hun-Hy, 1787. (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - I, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Ja-Je, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Jo-Ju, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Ka-Ke, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Ki-Ky, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - La, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Le, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Li, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Lo, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Lu-Ly, 1787. (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - McA-McCl, 1787. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - McCo-McCu, 1787. (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - McD-McI, 1787. (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - McI-McM, 1787. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - McN-McW, 1787. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Mad-Mar, 1787. (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Mas-May, 1787. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Me-Miller, 1787. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Millard-Mitchell, 1787. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Moa-Moo, 1787. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Mor-Mou, 1787. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Moses, Isaac, 1787. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Mu-My, 1787. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - N, 1787. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - 0, 1787. (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Pac-Par, 1787. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Pat-Pay, 1787. (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Pea-Pen, 1787. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Pennell, Joseph and Thomas, 1787. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Per-Peu, 1787. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Ph-Pla, 1787. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Pleasants, 1787. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Po, 1787. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Pr-Pu, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - P - Miscellaneous, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Q, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Ra, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Raguet, Nicholas, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Rea-Ree, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Reed, John, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Rei-Rev, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Ri, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Rob, 1787. (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Rod-Roy, 1787. (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Ru, 1787. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Sa-Sc, 1787. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Se-Sha, 1787. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - She-Sho, 1787. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Si-Sl, 1787. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Sm-Sn, 1787. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - So-Sp, 1787. (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Sta-Ste, 1787. (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Sti-Sto, 1787. (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Str-Sy, 1787. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Ta, 1787. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Te, 1787. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Thom, 1787. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Thor-Ti, 1787. (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - To-Tr, 1787. (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Tu, 1787. (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - U, 1787. (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - V, 1787. (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Wa, 1787. (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - We, 1787. (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Wh, 1787. (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Wic-Williamson, 1787. (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Willis-Wilson, 1787. (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Win-Wit, 1787. (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Wo, 1787. (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Wr-Wy, 1787. (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Y, 1787. (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Z, 1787. (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified, 1787. (Box 86, Folder 7)
- 1788
  - Ad-Ap, 1788. (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Ar-Au, 1788. (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Ba, 1788. (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Be, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Bi-Bl, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Bo, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Bra-Bry, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Brown, Israel, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Bruin, Peter Bryan, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Bu, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Cab-Cam, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Cap-Cas, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Ch, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Cl, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Co, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Cr-Cu, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Dan-Davey, 1788. (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Davies-Daw, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - De, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Deakins, Francis and William, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Di, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Do-Du, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - E, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Fa-Fi, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Fl-Fr, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Fu, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Ga, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Gi-Go, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Gr-Gw, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Hai-Ham, 1788. (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Han, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Hard-Harr, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Hart-Hay, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - He, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Hi, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Hob-Hon, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Hoo-How, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Hu-Hy, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - I, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Ja, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Je-Ji, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Jo, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Ka-Ke, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Ki-Kr, 1788. (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - La, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Le-Li, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Lo-Lu, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Mac-Man, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Mar, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Mas-Maz, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - McC, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - McF-McR, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Me, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Mi, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Minnis, Robert, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Mo, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Mu-My, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Na, 1788. (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Nea-Nee, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Nel-Nez, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Ni-Nu, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - O, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Pa, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Pe-Ph, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Pi-Po, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Pr, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Pu, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Q, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Ra-Ri, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Rob-Row, 1788. (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Roy-Ru, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Sa-Se, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Sha-She, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Shi-Shu, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Si-Sm, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Richard, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Richard, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Richard, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Richard, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Richard, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Richard, 1788. (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Sn-Sr, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Sta-Ste, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Sti-Sto, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Str-Sw, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - S- unidentified, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Ta, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Tarrison, Bartholomew, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Te-Tr, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Tu-Ty, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - U, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - V, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Wa, 1788. (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Walker, 1788. (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Watkins, 1788. (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - We, 1788. (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Wh-Wi, 1788. (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Wo-Wy, 1788. (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Y, 1788. (Box 94, Folder 6)
- 1789
  - Ab-An, 1789. (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Ar-Ay, 1789. (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Ba-Benn, 1789. (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Bens-Brig, 1789. (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Brit-By, 1789. (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Ca-Carre, 1789. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Carri-Cl, 1789. (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Co-Cra, 1789. (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Cro-Cu, 1789. (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Da-Di, 1789. (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Do-Du, 1789. (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - E, 1789. (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Fa-Fi, 1789. (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Fl-Fu, 1789. (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Ga-Go, 1789. (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Gr-Gw, 1789. (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Ha, 1789. (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - He-Hol, 1789. (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Hop-Hu, 1789. (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - I, 1789. (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - J, 1789. (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - K, 1789. (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - La-Le, 1789. (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Li-Ly, 1789. (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Ma, 1789. (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Mc, 1789. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Me-Mi, 1789. (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Mo-Mu, 1789. (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - N, 1789. (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - O, 1789. (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Pa-Pe, 1789. (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Pi-Pu, 1789. (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Q, 1789. (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Ra-Robe, 1789. (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Robi-Ry, 1789. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Sa-Sh, 1789. (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Si-Sm, 1789. (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Sn-Ste, 1789. (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Sto-Sy, 1789. (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Ta-Ti, 1789. (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - To-Tu, 1789. (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - U, 1789. (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - V, 1789. (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Wa, 1789. (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - We-Wo, 1789. (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Y, 1789. (Box 100, Folder 8)
- 1790
  - A, 1790. (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Ba-Be, 1790. (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Bi-Bu, 1790. (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Ca-Ch, 1790. (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Cl-Cu, 1790. (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - D, 1790. (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - E, 1790. (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - F, 1790. (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - G, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Ha-He, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Hi-Hy, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - I-J, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - K, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - L, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Ma-Mc, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Me-Mo, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - N, 1790. (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - O, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - P-Q, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - R, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Sa-Si, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Sk-Sp, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - St-Sy, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - T, V, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Wa-Wilds, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Williams-Wo, 1790. (Box 103, Folder 9)
- 1791
  - Aa-An, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Ar-Ba, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Be-Bi, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Bl-Br, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Bu-Cap, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Car-Ci, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Cl-Col, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Con-Coy, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Cr-Cu, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Da-De, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Di, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Do-Du, 1791. (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - E, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - F, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - G, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Hai-Harp, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Harr-Hay, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - He-Hi, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Ho, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Hu, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Hunt, Ralph, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Ja-Johnson, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Johnston-Ju, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Ke-Ki, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Kn-Ky, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - La-Le, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Lo-Ly, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Mab-Mar, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Mas-Max, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - McC, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - McD-McQ, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Me, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Mi, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Mon-Morgan, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Morr, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Mort-Mu, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - N, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - O, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Pa, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Pe-Pi, 1791. (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Po-Pr, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Q, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Ra-Re, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Rh-Ri, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Ro, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Sa-Sc, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Se-Si, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Sl-So, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Sp-Ste, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Sti-Sy, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Ta-Th, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Ti-Ty, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - V, 1791. (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Wa-Wh, 1791. (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Wi, 1791. (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Wo-Wy, 1791. (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Y, 1791. (Box 108, Folder 4)
- 1792
  - Ad-An, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Ar-Ay, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Ba, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Be, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Bi-Bl, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Bo, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Br, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Bu, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Cab-Cal, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Calbreath, James, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Cam-Cas, 1792. (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Ch-Cl, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Cob-Con, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Coo-Cox, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Cr, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Cu, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Da, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - De-Di, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Do, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Dr-Du, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Ea-El, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Er-Ew, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Fa-Fl, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Fo-Fu, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Forde, Standish, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Ga, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Gi-Go, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Gra-Gree, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Greg-Gu, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Hac-Han, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Hanway, Samuel and Forde, Standish, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Har, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Has-Hay, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - He, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Hi-Ho, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Hu-Hy, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - I, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - J, 1792. (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Johnston-Jones, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Ka-Kin, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Kir-Ku, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - La-Le, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Li-Ly, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Mac-Man, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Mar, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Mas-May, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Mc, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Me-Mi, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Mof-Mor, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Mos-Mu, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - N, 1792. (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Newell, James and Samuel, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - O, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - O'Mealy, Michael, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Pa, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Pe, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Ph-Pi, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Pl-Po, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Pr-Pu, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Preston, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Ra-Re, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Rh-Ri, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Ro, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Ru-Ry, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Sa-Se, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Sh, 1792. (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Si-Sm, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Smith/Smyth, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - So-Sp, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - St, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Su-Sy, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Tag-Tat, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Tay-Te, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Th-To, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Tr-Ty, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - U, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - V, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Wad-Wam, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - War-Wax, 1792. (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - We, 1792. (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Wh-Wi, 1792. (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Williams, 1792. (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, 1792. (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Wo-Wr, 1792. (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Y, 1792. (Box 115, Folder 6)
- 1793
  - A-Al, 1793. (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - An-Ay, 1793. (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Ba, 1793. (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Be, 1793. (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Bi-Bl, 1793. (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Bo-Br, 1793. (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Bu-By, 1793. (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Ca-Cam, 1793. (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Cap-Cat, 1793. (Box 117, Folder 1)